

ABOUT ME

As a computer programmer, I think my experience with the technical side could really help in the process of developing software. My goal is to provide programming solutions. So that it could be used in all products and all services and also bring entrepreneurship spirit to the team giving my passion and experience working as a start up."

LINKS

Linkedin::

https://www.linkedin.com/in/wmn -nisal-a280651b6

GitHub::

https://github.com/wnsnisal

PERSONAL DETAILS

Date of birth 1992 june 28

Marital status Single

SOFT SKILLS

- Analytical and Problem-Solving Skills
- Project Management
- Creative thinking ability
- Leadership Skills
- Time Management
- Good Team Player
- Flexibility

NISAL HASINDU

ASSOCIATE SOFTWARE ENGINEER

231/2, Dibulwala road, kattange, kahawatta., Ratnapura, 70150, Sri Lanka

+94702556391

wmnhasindu@gmail.com

WORK EXPERIENCE

LOGISTICS BLOCKS LIMITED C/O

Cambridgeshire CB22 5NE, United Kingdom. Jun 2021 - Present

KYRAX SOLUTIONS

Thiriwanaketiya, Ratnapura Nov 2020 - Jun 2021

SABARAGAMU MAHA SAMAN DEWALAYA

Ratnapura Jan 2018 - Nov 2020

MONARA ADVERTISING

Kuruvita Jan 2017 - Jan 2018

THARUKA MASS ADVERTISING

Ratnapura Jan 2016 - Jan 2017

JUNIOR SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

Gained experience in Full Stack Development and blockchain technologies.

INTERN SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

Gained experience in Full Stack Development with PHP and experience with wordpress CMS.

MEDIA COORDINATOR

Gained experience events coordinator and graphic designing.

GRAPHIC DESIGNER

gained experience in graphic designing.

GRAPHIC DESIGNER

gained experience in graphic designing.

PROJECT EXPERIENCES

Jun 2019 - Aug 2019

"ONLINE LIBRARY MANAGEMENT SYSTEM" web design and development assignment in HND

Developed a web-based Library management system for handling books details, users details and admin details. TOOLS & TECHHNOLOGIES: PHP, MySQL, HTML5, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap

May 2018 - Jul 2018

"AYUBO DRIVE - VEHICLE RENT SYSTEM" HND - Programming assignment

Developed a Vehicle rent system (a desktop application) for renting vehicles and to calculate rent amounts and fees. TOOLS & TECHNOLOGIES: Visual Studio IDE, C#

Aug 2018 - Nov 2018

"TRANSPORT MANAGEMENT SYSTEM" HND-Database assignment

A transport management system for handle delivering goods and handling transports.

TOOLS & TECHNOLOGIES: Visual Studio IDE, C#

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- JAVA
- C#
- Python
- PHP
- MySQL / Mongo dB
- HTML / CSS /
- JavaScript/ NodeJs
- Word press
- React js / Codeigniter 4
- Flutter
- Git version control
- Bootstrap /Material UI
- Figma, Adobe XD, photoshop, illustrator

NON-RELATED REFEREES

Mr. P. Pavithra Piyumal Branch Manager ESOFT METRO COLLEGE – Ratnapura. No: 56/2, Bandaranayake

Mawatha, Ratnapura. Phone : (+94)77 3101216 Email : <u>piyumal@esoft.lk</u>

Ms. D. Wickramaarchchi Retired Grama Niladari, Retired Grama Niladari – Muwagama Dayani, Aluketiya, Ratnapura. Phone : (+94)71 6081059 Jun 2020 - Aug 2021

"WORDPRESS WEBSITES"

Developed 3 websites using wordpress cms for self study.

- https://printme.website/
- http://drivingacademy.website/
- http://printup.website/

EDUCATION

ESOFT METRO COLLEGE

Ratnapura 2021

R/SIVALI CENTRAL COLLEGE

Ratnapura 2013

Higher National Diploma

(Looking forward to the diploma award)

GCE Advanced Level

Done G.C.E Advanced Level Examination with 1C pass.

COURSE

ESOFT METRO COLLEGE Jan 2017

Diploma in Web engineering

DECLARATION

I hereby certify that the given particulars are true and accurate to the best of my knowledge.

W.M.Nisal Hasindu 12/10/2121